<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Little Rock .NET User Group</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>LRDNUG Holiday Social and Board Member Election</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us Wednesday, December 11th at 5:30 PM for our annual Holiday Social and Board Member Election!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for people who are interested in being involved with the Little Rock .NET User Group and there are several openings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a chance to meet new and old members without a rigid schedule and program. Enjoy food and treats, prizes,
and also please bring items for donating to Dorca’s House Charity (http://bit.ly/2B8Nc49)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/LRDNUG-Holiday-Social-and-Board-Member-Election/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/LRDNUG-Holiday-Social-and-Board-Member-Election/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spicing up your Code with Curry</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All encounters must begin with an introduction. This introduction is not to a tool or a new code library.We are not going to discuss a particular language. I want to introduce you to the functional programming paradigm. Except, we will not be diving in head first. Instead we will focus on just a single technique that demonstrates the mindset of functional programming, Currying. This would be similar to just dipping your toes into the pool of functional programming. There will be a bit of history, a review of everyday code, some curry ,and hopefully you depart with a new way to approach programming tasks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-the-speaker&quot;&gt;About the Speaker&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m an Arkansas raised computer scientist currently applying my skills at Arkansas Children’s Hospital. Specifically, data analytics and system integrations. As a programmer, I am a tinkerer. The pleasure of using a new technique, a new tool, adjusting a program, preforming a workflow analysis is entertaining.  I have been attending the .NET user group meetings on and off again for years.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Spicing-up-your-Code-with-Curry/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Spicing-up-your-Code-with-Curry/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Walk in the Clouds, Understanding Cloud Options in a Multicloud World</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free craft beer! Plus, we will discuss various types of cloud services offerings, and how to determine the best fit for each application. We’ll also discuss why using multiple cloud platforms, rather than picking one, is better for organizations&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-the-speaker&quot;&gt;About the Speaker&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Johnny Earnest is a Solution Architect at Expedient. The Memphis Expedient data center is part of a network of eleven nationwide data centers, and offers a wide range of managed services such as virtualization, cloud computing, remote backups, management of equipment, storage area networks, disaster recovery and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before joining Expedient Johnny worked in Ericsson’s Global Services Cloud Center of Excellence. At Ericsson, he worked with customers to rollout Ericsson’s new Hyperscale Datacenter System line of servers, the world’s first complete system based on Intel’s Rack Scale Design software-defined infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnny spent 17 years working for Hewlett Packard. As a Distinguished Technologist in HP’s Global Solutions Architecture &amp;amp; Engineering organization, Johnny worked with HP’s most strategic customers with a focus on mission critical computing, cloud, and big data. He built and led technical teams to work must-win sales opportunities, lead countless technical escalations, spearheaded new product introductions, and lead global complex migrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnny served in a global role for over a decade, and grew up living abroad. Johnny holds a BS in Computer Science, with a minor in Business Management from Union University. Johnny has three kids, a passion for mentoring at-risk youth, and fosters dogs through Middle Tennessee Boxer Rescue. He resides in Arlington, Tennessee&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/A-Walk-in-the-Clouds-Understanding-Cloud-Options-in-an-Multicloud-World/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/A-Walk-in-the-Clouds-Understanding-Cloud-Options-in-an-Multicloud-World/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Overcoming Delay - How The Best Developers Increase Productivity</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overcoming Delay: How The Best Developers Increase Productivity In the software industry, it’s common to be on a project with an aggressive timeline. Even if the schedule was correct, plans don’t always go the way you expect and become off track. Teams end up working more extended hours, try to add people to the project or make other heroic efforts to try and “save the day’ and finish on time. In my experience, rarely have those efforts worked and when it did, the team was so burned out it took several weeks to get motivated to tackle another project. There should be a better way to complete projects on time, so teams feel a sense of accomplishment and are excited to take on the next project. In this session, we discuss three key behaviors you can do with your team, unlocking a better way to work to help the team succeed. 
Learning outcomes: Learn how to improve the flow of how you get work done by not focusing on efficiency. Learn why being busy is not always the best way to get more work done. Learn and understand what a pull system is and how it can help your team work better. Realize that many of our natural instincts are not what we should listen to in order to get work done efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-the-speaker&quot;&gt;About the Speaker&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul Gower CTO, Speaker, AKT, Kanban Practitioner As a software developer since 2001, Paul has worked on a variety of projects and in many roles ranging from software developer to project lead. An innovative problem solver, he uses in-depth analysis, deep consultation, and the latest software development practices to serve his clients by helping them improve the predictability of their projects. Since 2016, Paul has become obsessed with learning how to help knowledge work teams work better by using agile principles and a Kanban mindset. Although he spends some of his time developing software for a select few clients, the rest of his time is spent training and coaching teams on how they can work better. Paul is an Accredited Kanban Trainer and constantly learning new ways to improve his client’s projects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Overcoming-Delay-How-The-Best-Developers-Increase-Productivity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Overcoming-Delay-How-The-Best-Developers-Increase-Productivity/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roundtable Presenters: From Azure to Z80</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Topic 1 - Abby Sims
A quick walkthrough of how we employ Azure DevOps for code/build management and Azure infrastructure for a recent client project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Topic 2 - Travis Jones
Retro Coding with Modern Tooling - Things I learned while writing a demo for the Game Boy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Topic 3 - YOU!
If you have a recent project you’d like to share with the group, email us at officers@lrdnug.org&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-the-speakers&quot;&gt;About the Speakers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abby Sims is a full stack software developer with 19 years of experience. She is President and Founder of Idestini, a software agency in Bryant. Abby is focused on developing custom software solutions that save businesses time and money, freeing clients to do the work they really want to be doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travis Jones is a software developer that focuses on modernizing services in the financial industry. He particularly enjoys automation of all kinds, as well as MSSQL development and optimization.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Roundtable-Presenters-From-Azure-to-Z80/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Roundtable-Presenters-From-Azure-to-Z80/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get to know the George W. Donaghey Emerging Analytics Center</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The George W. Donaghey Emerging Analytics Center™ (EAC) is a virtual and augmented reality, visualization, and interactive technology research center housed at the University of Arkansas at Little Rock. The mission of the EAC focuses on applied research expertise in the areas of immersive and interactive visualization for complex and big data problems in industry, government, and research organizations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The energetic group of faculty, researchers, and students at the EAC performs innovative research by incorporating technology, infrastructure, and application development in virtual and augmented reality. The EAC advances knowledge and the use of technology for the promotion of industrial growth, product development, social interaction, virtual collaboration, and the future of engaging in synthetic environments to solve real-world problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the EAC, students learn the technological tools and platforms that respond to the needs of a wide range of projects and audiences. The EAC develops solutions independent of individual technologies through employing a full toolbox of VR technologies for researching and developing new platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;directions&quot;&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emerging Analytics Center
U A Little Rock
2801 S. University Ave.
EIT Bldg. Room 418
Little Rock, AR 72204
501-569-8140&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directions from 630
University Ave. south
Left on 28th
Right on Campus Drive
next right into Lot 8
through the parking gate
The EIT building is on the left
Room 420&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PARKING
The gate to Lot8 will be open. If there are no spots available, the next best place to park is in Lot 13 near the Jack Stevens Center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOOD
As always, there will be pizza, drinks, and a dessert!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Get-to-know-the-George-W-Donaghey-Emerging-Analytics-Center/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Get-to-know-the-George-W-Donaghey-Emerging-Analytics-Center/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Build a successful remote agile team in three easy steps!</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many agile coaches think it’s a prerequisite to be a co-located team to be successful. However, what if you have has remote workers or are considering adding them to your team but afraid it will only slow you down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As more people choose to work remote it will be important to learn how to be a part of or lead successful remote agile teams. We will discuss three mindset changes that are critical to helping your team, regardless of location, implement agile and lean principals to help your team be a successful agile team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-the-speaker&quot;&gt;About the Speaker&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul started his career as a software developer in 2001 developing client/server enterprise solutions. An innovative problem solver, Paul uses in-depth analysis, deep consultation and the latest software development practices to serve his clients. In 2014 Paul started his company Lunamark (http://lumamark.com), where he leverages his years of experience to help companies improve their software development team’s efficiency using techniques such as clean coding practices, code reviews, pair programming, and Kanban. Paul is a certified Kanban Management Professional, Kanban Training for HugeIO (http://huge.io), and is constantly learning new ways to improve flow efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Build-A-Successful-Remote-Agile-Team/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Build-A-Successful-Remote-Agile-Team/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microsoft's Recent Mixed Reality Announcements</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE LOCATION CHANGE FOR MARCH! Thompson Library – Central Arkansas Library System, 38 Rahling Cir, Little Rock, AR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come learn about recent announcement related to Microsoft’s Mixed Reality platforms and tools from Jesse McCulloch, a Mixed Reality Developer Relations Program Manager at Microsoft. Jesse will be joining us in a remote live session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pizza and drinks provided. Prize raffle of software licenses and more at end of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-the-speaker&quot;&gt;About the Speaker&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting as a Mixed Reality Developer in 2016, Jesse has built up a strong community around HoloLens and Immersive Headsets, and then joined Microsoft in 2018. This gives him a very unique perspective and a strong desire to advocate strongly for the developers who are supporting the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is often found hanging out in the HoloDevelopers Slack group, and on Twitter trying to keep up with everything going on in this rapidly growing space.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Microsoft-Recent-Mixed-Reality-Announcements/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Microsoft-Recent-Mixed-Reality-Announcements/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Progressive Web Apps for .NET and Angular Developers</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us Tuesday, February 12th at 5:30 PM for our latest meetup! In this presentation, Google Developer Expert and awarded Microsoft MVP, Chander Dhall will take you from beginner to advanced level with Progressive Web Apps. The presentation includes, but is not limited to caching, offline support, app shell architecture, tools for building service workers, mobile web payments, and credentials management, add to homescreen, push notifications and best practices&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-the-speaker&quot;&gt;About the Speaker&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chander Dhall, CEO of Cazton, is an awarded Microsoft MVP, Google Developer Expert and world-renowned technology leader in architecting and implementing solutions. He’s not only rescued software development teams, but also implemented successful projects under tight deadlines and difficult business constraints. His company has a proven track record of not just saving the client millions of dollars, but also providing an expedited delivery time. Chander’s team of experts are internationally-acclaimed speakers in top technical conferences in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Progressive-Web-Apps-for-.NET-and-Angular-Developers/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Progressive-Web-Apps-for-.NET-and-Angular-Developers/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LRDNUG Holiday Social and Officer Election</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us Tuesday, December 11th at 5:30 PM for our annual Holiday Social and Officer Election!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a chance to meet new and old members without a rigid schedule and program. Enjoy food and treats, prizes,
and also please bring items for donating to Dorca’s House Charity (http://bit.ly/2B8Nc49)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/LRDNUG-Holiday-Social-and-Officer-Election/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/LRDNUG-Holiday-Social-and-Officer-Election/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>